<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About</title><link>https://robinwords.com/</link><description>Recent content on About</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://robinwords.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Angel Again</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/angel_again/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/angel_again/</guid><description>Wrapped up by his three year-old arms, comfortably curled up into his tiny lap, she slept. Secure in the knowledge that no harm would befall her.
384 days had passed since they had met, and 318 since she found the letter. Although she had never admitted it to herself, somewhere deep inside, she had known. As she read the words she smiled. She read, &amp;quot;Happy birthday Jason. We hope you will cherish this toy as much as your grandfather did when he was young.</description></item><item><title>That Game</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/that_game/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/that_game/</guid><description>Somehow, I knew; I wondered and waited, but deep down I knew. I saw the picture and all doubts were confirmed. I had lost.
Letting out a shaky laugh I looked up at him, meeting his dark eyes, and then glanced away, my face burning in shame and embarrassment. &amp;quot;You won,&amp;quot; I croaked out, scratching my cheek, trying to sound nonchalant. &amp;quot;I&amp;hellip; I fell in love first&amp;hellip;&amp;quot; He looked almost surprised, and then his eyes clouded over, as if he was thinking about something hard and foreign.</description></item><item><title>The Girl In The Stars</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_girl_in_the_stars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_girl_in_the_stars/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;I free the warrior, daughter of time, betrayed through love&amp;rdquo; a beautiful yet powerful looking face appeared in the stars. She had black-brown hair, harsh gold eyes and sepia skin. her lips were curved in a just smile, her eyes flashing. &amp;ldquo;I free the warrior&amp;rdquo; the girl&amp;rsquo;s body materilized , and appeared to the ground. &amp;ldquo;Thank you,&amp;rdquo; she said &amp;ldquo;Now who do we hunt?&amp;rdquo; She asked, holding her weapons. &amp;ldquo;Everyone.&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Going, Going, Gone</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/going_going_gone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/going_going_gone/</guid><description>With his free hand he was able to get to his phone.
It was Oliver whose mother has just died. He stared at the flashing caller-id in apprehension; how on earth did you comfort someone so dislikable?
The answer was simple, you didn&amp;rsquo;t, so he let it ring in the darkness of his room, his mind telling him to pick up, but his personal grudge saying no.
He had more important things to worry about than Oliver- Oliver who used to be so kind, Oliver who used to be his best friend, Oliver who had apologized, Oliver, who, maybe, had been sincere.</description></item><item><title>Outside In</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/outside_in/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/outside_in/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t touch it!&amp;rdquo; yelled Crowley &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip;it&amp;hellip;changes things!&amp;rdquo;. but it was too late. to crowley&amp;rsquo;s horror, josh held the gold statue. &amp;quot;Crowley, you are crazy.&amp;quot; but then. crowley and josh scremed in agony and pain as they changed: josh suddenly grew large raven wings, crowley had fangs. &amp;quot;Ahh!&amp;quot; both boys yelled, looking at each other. Their flesh began to disintegrate, falling to the floor as thick piles of noxious fluid and sagging skin.</description></item><item><title>Mystical Forest Lady</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/mystical_forest_lady/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/mystical_forest_lady/</guid><description>Alone in the forest was a young woman with the most lovely golden hair ever. With her back to the tallest tree she takes in the sounds of the forest. Wind and air rushing past leaves, the rumpling melody in time with the gust whirling her hair. her eyes green as a leaf, she whispers to me &amp;quot;don&amp;rsquo;t be scared&amp;quot;
Slowly backing away, i see her start to be hidden be the trees.</description></item><item><title>The Entry Point</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_entry_point/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_entry_point/</guid><description>If I hadn&amp;rsquo;t stumbled splashing into the stream in the night, if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t thrown my soaked pants over the tree limb and crawled, shivering, into my sleeping bag, if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t pulled the jeans roughly down in the morning when I heard voices coming, if my yank hadn&amp;rsquo;t brought the limb of the tree low and revealed the doorknob above it on the trunk of the tree- if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t gone on the trip at all, the boundaries of my world would not have stretched and shifted this summer.</description></item><item><title>The End</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_end/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_end/</guid><description>She lived in her parents&amp;rsquo; house for years. The windows were tightly locked- the shades taped to allow no light inside. The only light that came in was from the small, hairline cracks of the dusty roof of the single story house; but the light was dirty and it was weak. Sometimes, there would be rats that would squeak past her, over her, sometimes they would get stuck in her long hair.</description></item><item><title>Drama Girl</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/drama_girl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/drama_girl/</guid><description>&amp;rdquo; Hey, dork&amp;rdquo; Britany snickered, her brown hair in a strait cheer leader ponytail, her 10000$ dollar outfit flawless. &amp;ldquo;Oh, back off,&amp;rdquo; I snapped, my red hair extremly tight curly, my makeup probaly smudged. &amp;ldquo;Oh, look&amp;rsquo;s like nerd girl is mad. too bad. i do not care,&amp;rdquo; She smirked, and sashayed away with her clone-like friends. &amp;ldquo;I hate Miss drama girl&amp;rdquo; I said harshly and grumbled off.
And then I realized that this was all pointless!</description></item><item><title>Kepay</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/kepay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/kepay/</guid><description>She appears with the ice cold wind and snow, comepleting the cycle and remaining the balance. They say the hair around her face and tumbling down her back is like ice. They say it&amp;rsquo;s white and there&amp;rsquo;s something about the way it moves. They say her eyes are the most pristine shade of grey. She comes with the cold to guide those spirits who have lost their way to the frost.</description></item><item><title>Murdock</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/murdock/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/murdock/</guid><description>This time, he didn&amp;rsquo;t relish the feel of it; in fact the dead calm of the clearing caused Murdock to experience something he had never known before, fear. Fear had always ruled cowards and children, but never an elite Order of the Balance assassin, such as Murdock. The Order represented a rare collection of men who all exhibited complete disregard for any creed or belief except justice, and therefore restored balance to the world.</description></item><item><title>The Best Story Y&#39;All Ever Heard!</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_best_story_yall_ever_heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_best_story_yall_ever_heard/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Now gather &amp;lsquo;round, boys! This is gonna be the best story y&amp;rsquo;all ever heard!&amp;rdquo; In the saloon, it seems like everyone says that. But almost everyone is looking at the man telling the story. &amp;ldquo;Now, I ain&amp;rsquo;t the kind of person t&amp;rsquo; brag, but have you ever heard about the time I was surrounded by the Wilson brothers? T&amp;rsquo;was a dark and stormy night. It was the best night I ever had because it was summer, until the Wilson brothers came in.</description></item><item><title>Totally Awesome Stuffs With No Prior Story</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/totally_awesome_stuffs_with_no_prior_story/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/totally_awesome_stuffs_with_no_prior_story/</guid><description>I look into the cave. I have to go in, or the beast will catch up with me. All there is to see is darkness. Who knows what could be in there? The beast&amp;rsquo;s heavy footsteps are becoming louder&amp;hellip; Closer&amp;hellip; Surely the beast can hear my heartbeat, or smell the raw fear welling up inside me. The ground shook mightily from the force of his steps; though I could not yet see the beast behind me.</description></item><item><title>Stereotypes</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/stereotypes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/stereotypes/</guid><description>I walked into the school that first day, I see some of my old friends from 8th grade standing in a small cluster by the some of lockers. I start to walk over to them when suddenly, they start to walk away. Never being one to catch on too quickly, I ran after them.
But they started to run away rather than just walk. I tried calling out to them, but they ignored me.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Bernard</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/mr_bernard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/mr_bernard/</guid><description>Mr. Bernard wasn&amp;rsquo;t your typical janitor. He was actually quite strange&amp;hellip; every afternoon at exactly 5:00, he would disappear into his janitor closet and not come out for 45 minutes. People who worked in the building wondered what Mr. Bernard did in his closet so they went to inspect. When they opened the door to investigate, it was empty with the exception of all the custodial supplies. Upon walking inside, they heard laughter inside the wall across from the closet&amp;rsquo;s entrance.</description></item><item><title>The Meal</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_meal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_meal/</guid><description>The rawboned young man sat lonely at a table in a restaurant, staring at the shadows of the candle-lit table. Just a few hours ago, he had been counting the few coins he had gathered at today&amp;rsquo;s harmonica-playing in the streets, several of which were coins he didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize and would not be able to spend. He liked to save them anyway and put them back in the cap the next day, so that it would look like he had already got plenty of money.</description></item><item><title>Forward</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/forward/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/forward/</guid><description>Jason felt like a failure. His classmates trying to help him only made it worse - their caressing fingers elongated into thick vines, wrapping around him; their soft words sounded as sirens. The nostalgic feeling of friendship seldom came for Jason, which slowly constriced his sense of worth like a python.
But he didn&amp;rsquo;t understand one thing; why did he crare ? He was creating his own monsters out of his friends, or were they real ?</description></item><item><title>Chicken</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/chicken/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/chicken/</guid><description>A pair of beady eyes gleamed in the darkness, distracting me from sleep. I sat up quickly and saw the body that the eyes belonged to at the foot of my bed. But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a human body The moaning and chilled air suggested something else&amp;hellip; something darker
It felt awful. The fealing that &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; thing was giving me shone darckly of a desire. A desire to destroy the world, a desire to kill anything in its way, a desire &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; to kill me.</description></item><item><title>The Butterknife</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_butterknife/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_butterknife/</guid><description>Marissa glanced uneasily at the greasy butterknife that sat on her kitchen table. Upon inspecting it closely, she found that though caked thick with the white grease, the knife had a variety of crumbs, all in different stages of the molding prosess She could still see her own reflection, even though the knife crumbs covering the knife were moldy. There was just enough unmarred metal on the blade that she could tell it was, indeed a knife - otherwise, she might have thought it a pen, a crust of bread, even a scrap of paper, for it was thoroughly encased in a rotting shell of old crumbs.</description></item><item><title>Gravity</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/gravity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/gravity/</guid><description>As he climed into the cockpit of the hovering machine, he got ready for what might be the most important race of his life. He harnessed himself in place and pulled his goggle down over his eyes &amp;quot;this is it&amp;quot; he thought to himself. He had waited for this moment for years. Hoping and praying that he would get here. But now that he was he had other things on his mind.</description></item><item><title>The Table</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_table/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_table/</guid><description>They each sat across from each other at a table. They were bound to their chairs but able to move their arms and heads. They could hardly see in the dark and had been informed that the only way they could see their families again is if they chose to pick up a gun off of the table and shoot the other. One of them, named Robert Martin, had just finished a hard day at work selling phones for Cisco.</description></item><item><title>Empty Fields</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/empty_fields/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/empty_fields/</guid><description>Somehow I got this far, midnight crescent moon lit walks beside the point until yesterday I thought I was doing okay doing without but now I feel like like an echo&amp;rsquo;s echo merely a shadow beneath the blinding sun bleached out drained and left out for the wind to blow me like a man made plastic Walmart bag dancing alone across the big and empty fields outside my home.
Of course that home, among many other things, is gone now.</description></item><item><title>Darkness...</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/darkness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/darkness/</guid><description>Darkness as far as the eye can see shows not a glimpse of the light, but the light of a glimpse. So brilliant is the light, that unwary travelers were often lured to the dark forest thinking the glimpse was refuge, rather than the deadly evil it represented. Eeltu Fosgah dwelled within that darkness and had been a evil malevolent force since the end of the Q&amp;rsquo;antir Elemental Wars. Coll Merdit was one of the few who was unaffected by the stories, legends, and mysteries lurking within Wescan forest To him, Eeltu Fosgah was literary fodder for bedtime children&amp;rsquo;s stories, and not considered a viable threat to Coll&amp;rsquo;s village, Every so often, brave sounding men would muster their courage, give big speeches about eliminating the source of their anxiety, and then do absolutely nothing but cower in their homes like the rest.</description></item><item><title>The Diamond Flame</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_diamond_flame/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_diamond_flame/</guid><description>I felt ashamed. Here I had the whole world laugh at me using my invention. I wanted to hide away in my own dimension of magic away from technology, problems, and the world.
However, I didn&amp;rsquo;t see all of the problems in my world. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really understand it nearly as well as I thought i had. Some doors are best left shut. It took me years to find this truth.</description></item><item><title>The Game</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_game/</guid><description>Aaron likes games. Some of Aaron&amp;rsquo;s games had grownup matters in them, such as taxes and work. One day, the company behind Aaron&amp;rsquo;s favorite series of tax and work based games was acquired by EA. Aaron, being a loyal fan of the series, bought the new entry in the series after the corporate takeover. &amp;quot;All these review sites say this game is perfect, so I should buy it!&amp;quot; said Aaron to no one in particular as he bought the game on his computer.</description></item><item><title>Twisted Consequences</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/twisted_consequences/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/twisted_consequences/</guid><description>Ben lay in his bed, topless, tapping mindlessly at his computer. It was 4:37 and he knew he should have be sleeping, but it was only in the middle of the night where he felt sane, not-quite happy, but content. There was no-one to bother him and he could do really what ever he wanted. He had to go to tutoring tomorrow morning and he felt almost certain he would fall asleep in the middle of it.</description></item><item><title>We Knew</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/we_knew/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/we_knew/</guid><description>Darkness. I can&amp;rsquo;t say it was a pleasant experience, but something about the cold wrap of the wind off the water, the moon peering through the cave opening above, was almost comforting in a way. The shivering feeling that travels up my spine when I stare deep into the moon, the bloodlust, it consumes me. For a moment, I wished I hadn&amp;rsquo;t decided to make this trek in the middle of the night, but then I remembered why I had come.</description></item><item><title>The Gift</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_gift/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_gift/</guid><description>I knew it was the last time I&amp;rsquo;d see him. In his brusque, clench-toothed replies, his furrowed brow, his down-turned chin, I could feel the finality of it all. The train was going to depart in an hour, so i had to help him dress, pack his worldly possessions, then lead him to the taxi-cab waiting outside.
&amp;quot;where to guv&amp;rsquo;nor?&amp;quot; the taxi driver asked us?
I sighed. &amp;quot;Take us to the East Ramsey Train Station.</description></item><item><title>Corruption</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/corruption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/corruption/</guid><description>Power, one of the many things that can corrupt a person&amp;rsquo;s life. One who has power has nothing, indeed, but the power to make people think that power is real; that power can control their lives - thus, a corruption is born. Had people in this cruel world of 3004 realized the bozmarks were controling every aspect of their lives ; well it would be a much different story. Of course, I the hero noticed, I Samueli Warco, saved them all from the monsterous people turned into bozmarks.</description></item><item><title>The Bug</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_bug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_bug/</guid><description>I was walking down the street when I realised, there was a bug in my hair. I noticed it in the most unpleasant manner of reaching to adjust my hat, upon which I shortly discovered the bug, clinging to my right earlobe.
As I looked closer at the bug, I was astonished, it possessed a quite unique pattern determining that it was a rare species. So I pulled out my field guide only to discover something very bizarre.</description></item><item><title>The Godfather</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_godfather/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_godfather/</guid><description>The godfather was a cruel and wicked man. His complexion was that of a turnip, a deathly white pallor accented with black-rimmed, sunken eyes, a well-defined chin, and thin, oily black hair slicked flat against his head. He had a certain air of refinement to him, wafting through the chill rooms on his pale-lipped smile, his dusted suit, his black, heeled boots on the tile. One could have imagined him as dead, beyond the grave, without much else to work with - it was in his pale skin, lightly touched with yellow around the edges, in his fingertips, shelled in his long, ivory nails, in his slow, shambling walk, carefully perfect: heel-toe, heel-toe.</description></item><item><title>Mystery In Falor Mansion</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/mystery_in_falor_mansion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/mystery_in_falor_mansion/</guid><description>A cold howl of wind zipped through the deserted house. It was a harsh, shallow sound, almost a rattling, or perhaps it was more of a thumping - but it was an eerie, haunted sound nonetheless.
Upstairs in the spare bedroom a window was open and through it crawled a person. This person had with him a bag, and in this bag was the body of Delanie Wilcox a 20 year old college student at Georgia Tech.</description></item><item><title>The Never-Ending Wait</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_neverending_wait/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_neverending_wait/</guid><description>I sat in the library cafe, surrounded by nine-year-olds from the school next door, and troubled and disabled kids with thier social workers, waiting for my dad to get off of work. While I waited, I watched the kids play tag together. They kept falling over and hurting themselves when they got tagged. Their feet were clumsy, their arms bumbling, and sometimes, their mouths would droop on one side against their will.</description></item><item><title>Empty</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/empty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/empty/</guid><description>There he laid. Only knowing of his fate, not of his origins, journey, nor his companions. The knowledge of his fate he dreaded. He had been told this day would come, but now as he stared at the ceiling he knew the end was near. The end of his naive nature, the end of his denial of who he really was. Now he had to face the man, but it could wait until morning.</description></item><item><title>Funny How These Things Work</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/funny_how_these_things_work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/funny_how_these_things_work/</guid><description>As she was flipping through some old photos in a Facebook album from long ago she noticed a man, well rather a boy then, in the front. It was just his back and his head, but she knew it was him. She had spent long enough watching him to know. He was the man she was now in love with, unrequited, but she hadn&amp;rsquo;t known him then. This picture was from an entire year before they had met.</description></item><item><title>Lost And Found</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/lost_and_found/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/lost_and_found/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Come on in, Lewis, it&amp;rsquo;s open,&amp;rdquo; Sharon called out loudly.
Lewis opened the door slowly, taking a deep breath before stepping into his sisters apartment. WHAT ARE YOU DOING screams Lewis when he saw Sharon in the kitchen. &amp;quot;Just preparing the turkey for tonight dear!&amp;quot; Sharon defended Lewis was sure that something was off, but he couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell what it might be Lewis excuses himself to the bathroom and begins to looks around.</description></item><item><title>Who Knows?</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/who_knows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/who_knows/</guid><description>They sat across the table staring at one another, contempt in their eyes. They knew what had to be done, but neither cared to speak of it. &amp;quot;Stop this!&amp;quot; the first finally yelled, slamming his fists on the table as he went, &amp;quot;I came here for answers that I was promised, not a staring contest.&amp;quot; It was a wage of war; you could see it in the other&amp;rsquo;s eyes, an inferno of hatred deep within, a flickering of knowledge, a smear of defiance.</description></item><item><title>Herping Of Derp</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/herping_of_derp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/herping_of_derp/</guid><description>Once there was a man named Moron, who lived in a house made of cabbages . I know what your thinking, &amp;quot;Cabbages make a lousy building material, especially for a house!&amp;quot;, but it was better than the only other alternative, peanut butter.
written by:
kimwilson113kim
syene137
Mugkaniarar</description></item><item><title>Lizard Lord</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/lizard_lord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/lizard_lord/</guid><description>The Lizard Lord had finally finished snacking on his favourite food, potatoes. Now it was time to snack on the flesh of his enemies. The first celebrity he devoured was so bad tasting, that he never ate humans again. The Lizard Lord then went on to make peace with his enemies, and neighbouring lands.
However, that was when&amp;hellip; THE WAFFLES INVADED!!!
&amp;quot;Yippee!&amp;quot; squealed the Lizard Lord, &amp;quot;I adore waffles, and maybe they will finally get rid of the taste of Kardashian in my mouth!</description></item><item><title>The Day Of The Robin</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_day_of_the_robin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_day_of_the_robin/</guid><description>The robin slowly moved across the grass, one foot at a time. He carefully looked for insects in the thick, tall grass. As he was sifting through the grass, he stumbled upon a small, shiny rock.
written by:
pletcherahv
pletcheroks
ccwyqiad</description></item><item><title>The Adventures Of Donald Trump And His Encounters With Dark Lord Cthulhu.</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_adventures_of_donald_trump_and_his_encounters_with_dark_lord_cthulhu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/the_adventures_of_donald_trump_and_his_encounters_with_dark_lord_cthulhu/</guid><description>Donald Trump woke up in an empty void. It was an endless blackness that expanded as far as the eye can see. A voice thundered from on high. It was maddening, and shook the earth, as it thundered down, &amp;ldquo;WHO DARES CROSS INTO MY REALM?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;quot;I cross into the best realms,&amp;quot; The Don replies.
&amp;quot;W&amp;hellip; WHA&amp;hellip; WHAT?&amp;quot;
A dark figure appeared in the void. Don lifted his eyes to look, and saw Kim Jong-un approaching in a menacing manner, a frown furrowed across his face.</description></item><item><title>My Earth-2 Fella.</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/my_earth2_fella/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/my_earth2_fella/</guid><description>I woke up in a different world but it was the same, I recognized everyone around me but they were different&amp;hellip;
Oddly different&amp;hellip;
They all looked like they usually would, but there was one distinct difference. They all had the same outfit on. The same orange prisoner jumpsuit.
written by:
vhbjrcml
sumafzom
stupcxfi</description></item><item><title>Global Intelligence</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/global_intelligence/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/global_intelligence/</guid><description>David stared at the wall beside him, there was something unnatural about this wall, but he just couldn&amp;rsquo;t work out what. Then he saw it. A crack. There was a crack in the wall that wasn&amp;rsquo;t there before.
written by:
wmopxtte
pletcherkjo
siwhzhwp</description></item><item><title>Alternative Time</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/alternative_time/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/alternative_time/</guid><description>Bob paced back and forth in his tiny office job cell. But having a tiny office job wasn&amp;rsquo;t on his mind at the moment, for he had just altered time and space itself.
It happened by mistake. He didn&amp;rsquo;t plan anything like that.
written by:
careteyroraj
bpwhpqpg</description></item><item><title>Paperboy</title><link>https://robinwords.com/stories/paperboy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/stories/paperboy/</guid><description>Being a paperboy is actually harder than I thought it would be.
I start on Morrison Avenue. Three blocks down is the Smithsons&amp;rsquo; aggressive dog. Take a left turn to avoid the Robinson house party. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to give out two copies for the maroon house with the brown roof. Finish the crossword puzzle for the children next door. At all costs, stay away from Harridan Street. I MUST. STAY. AWAY.</description></item><item><title>Game</title><link>https://robinwords.com/game/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://robinwords.com/game/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>